http://www.eepb.com/privacy-policy

CPAs and Business Advisors
HomeOur FirmServicesAssurance and Financial ReportingBusiness Advisory ServicesBusiness Transition ServicesEstate PlanningDentistryHealthcareLitigation SupportOil and GasR & D Tax CreditReal EstateSales TaxTax PlanningNewsContactResourcesTax ToolsTax Tips for IndividualsTax Tips for BusinessesTax Tips for FinancialTax RatesDue DatesFinancial ToolsRetention GuideIRS FormsFinancial GuidesBankingBusinessFinancialInsuranceLife EventsTaxesDirectorsCareersCurrent Job OpeningsCommunityClient Login
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Privacy Statement
EEPB PC respects your right to keep your personal information private and to avoid unwelcome solicitations.
Our Privacy Statement explains what type of information we collect, how we may use it, and under what circumstances we may share it.
Under no circumstance will we provide your personal information to non-EEPB PC companies for the purpose of telemarketing or mail marketing.
What information do we collect?
We collect personal information about you only when that information is provided by you or is obtained with your authorization. We use that information to provide the tax, accounting, financial planning, and other services you request.
We may collect this information through letters or e-mails from you, meetings or phone calls with you, documents you provide to us, and other means, as appropriate.
How do we use the information collected?
We may use your contact data to send you information about EEPB PC or our products or services, or promotional material, or to contact you when necessary.
We may use your financial information to provide the services you request.
Who do we share your information with?
Certain nonpublic information about you may be disclosed in the following specific situations:
1. To comply with a validly issued and enforceable subpoena or summons.
2. In the course of a review of EEPB PC's practices under the authorization of a state or national licensing board, review of our professional practice under AICPA or PCAOB authorization, or as necessary to properly respond to an inquiry or complaint from such a licensing board or organization.
3. As a part of any actual or threatened legal proceedings or alternative dispute resolution proceedings either initiated by or against us, provided we disclose only the information necessary to file, pursue, or defend against the lawsuit and take reasonable precautions to ensure that the information disclosed does not become a matter of public record.
4. In conjunction with the normal due diligence process of any merger, provided that we take appropriate precautions so the prospective merger partner does not disclose information obtained in the course of the process.
Who has access to your information?
In order to provide the best service possible, EEPB PC employees are permitted to access the information they need to perform their jobs. However, we maintain strict internal policies against unauthorized disclosure or use of client information.
Join Our Newsletter Here
Submit
FOLLOW US
Home
About Us
Services
Client Login
Contact
© 2020 EEPB, P.C.   All Rights Reserved.
Web Builder CS: Websites for Accountants
